<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[SnapOdds RSS feed]]></title><description><![CDATA[SnapOdds Website]]></description><link>https://zeitvertrieb.github.io/snapodds</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 08:53:36 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title><![CDATA[Meet us at SBC Summit North America and experience SnapOdds]]></title><description><![CDATA[Meet our Founder Thomas Willomitzer  and Co-Founder Matthias Grieder personally.
More information about the event you find at:  https…]]></description><link>https://zeitvertrieb.github.io/snapoddssbc/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://zeitvertrieb.github.io/snapoddssbc/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Meet our Founder Thomas Willomitzer&lt;/strong&gt; and Co-Founder Matthias Grieder personally.
More information about the event you find at: &lt;a href=&quot;https://sbcevents.com/sbc-summit-north-america/#about&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://sbcevents.com/&quot;&gt;https://sbcevents.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Connect on LinkedIn:&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Thomas Willomitzer &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/in/thomaswillomitzer/&quot;&gt;https://www.linkedin.com/in/thomaswillomitzer/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Matthias Grieder &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/in/matthias-grieder/&quot;&gt;https://www.linkedin.com/in/matthias-grieder/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Snapscreen partnership with Miomni, the leading B2B white label end-to-end solutions provider in the gaming industry.]]></title><description><![CDATA[We are happy to announce a partnership with Miomni, the leading B2B white label end-to-end solutions provider in the gaming industry…]]></description><link>https://zeitvertrieb.github.io/snapoddsmiomnipartner/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://zeitvertrieb.github.io/snapoddsmiomnipartner/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;We are happy to announce a partnership with Miomni, the leading B2B white label end-to-end solutions provider in the gaming industry. Snapscreen’s computer vision technology will be integrated into the apps of Miomni’s customers like Cesars, Stations Casinos, Golden Nugget and many more. We invented Shazam for sports betting. This ground breaking product which allows any customer to hold up a Miomni sports betting mobile app to any live game on any screen (TV at home or big screen in a bar) and the video recognition technology instantly takes the user straight to the bet on the live game that is being shown.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>